A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Photo Files, RG 1 FA1128
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller, Laurance S. and Family, 1880s - 2004; 9
  - Rockefeller, Mary French, Family, 1885-1999; 6
    - French, Mary Montagu Billings, Undated; Black and white 8x10 print (Box 58, Folder 905)
      Portrait, in fur hat. Removed from frame.
    - French, Mary Montagu Billings, Undated; Black and white 8x10 print with hard backing. (Box 58, Folder 906)
      Portrait, seated at desk in Woodstock mansion.
    - Hitchcock, Elizabeth French, 1920s-1930s; Brown tone 6.5 x 8.5 print in 8.5 x 12.5 portfolio frame (Box 58, Folder 907)
      Portrait by Edward F. Foley Studio, NY (undated).
    - Hitchcock, Elizabeth French and Family, 1937, circa 1955; OVERSIZED black and white 10.5 x 13 and 13.5 x 15 prints, one in portfolio mat. (Box O 96)
      Wedding photo of Elizabeth French and Ethan Allen Hitchcock; Elizabeth French in bridal gown with MFR, both holding bouquets. Photos by Ira L. Hill, 1937. Printed photograph of MFR and Elizabeth French, circa 1955, clipped from Life magazine
    - Hitchcock, Elizabeth French and Family, 1940s-1970s, undated; Black and white and color, 2 x 3.5 -9 x 11.5 (Box 58, Folder 908)
      Elizabeth French and Ethan Allen Hitchcock, daughters Constance and Mary Elizabeth, 1940s-1970s; 2 photos of grandchildren; nice image of Ethan and Elizabeth in Norway, circa 1974
    - Hitchcock, Elizabeth French and Family, 1950s; Black and white 5x7 photos. (Box 58, Folder 909)
      LSR and MFR flying with Elizabeth French and Ethan Hitchcock (interesting interior views of cabin interior); LSR playing billiards with Hitchcock and unidentified man; MFR dining at Woodstock with unidentified.
    - Hitchcock, Elizabeth French and Family, 1966; OVERSIZED color 11x14 print. Color faded and emulsion slightly crackled. (Box O 96)
      Elizabeth French and Ethan Allen Hitchcock with LSR and MFR, seated on top of a boat, departing from Ushuaia, Argentina. Image reproduced in National Geographic, January 1967. Removed from frame. Nice image, but in fair condition.
- Trips, 1930s - 2002; 10
  - General, 1940s - 1970s; 1
    - General (Europe), 1940s; Black and white prints, approximately 3x4 - 4x6. Some duplicate enlargements (Box 58, Folder 910)
      Europe. Artistic photos of street scenes, nuns with child, child's shoes, man with chickens.
    - General, 1940s; Black and white prints, 2.75 x 4.5, 4.75 x 6.75 (Box 58, Folder 911)
      LSR on board boat; LSR at pier with military man and jeep, sign reading Welcome Gen. Mrs. MacArthur; unidentified church, mountains; printed photo of indoor golf net.
    - General, 1950s; 2 color slides. (Box 58, Folder 912)
      Sailing of the United States, en route to the Congo? Two images of ship underway. Children watching from shore or boat.
    - General, 1950-1988, undated; Mainly color, 3.5x3.5-5x7 prints; 2 black and white. (Box 58, Folder 913)
      LSR and MFR together on various trips. Winter with (John and Eleanor French?), Caneel, unidentified places.
    - General, Circa 1960 and earlier; Small black and white and color prints, in leather 10 x 7.5 x 1.75 flip album. Some sleeves contain multiple photos; some deterioration of adhesives. Album unevenly filled with some sleeves overstuffed. (Box 59, Folder 914)
      Europe and U.S. General album of artistic, scenic, and personal photographs. Italy?, England?, U.S. Includes photos of MFR and others. (Possibly a student photo project)
    - General, 1964-1967; 14 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 59, Folder 915)
      Aerial views of Alaska, 1964. Images of LSR and others at Expo 67 (Montreal); ocean views. Section labeled "Misc. (MFR)."
    - General, 1960s-1970s, Undated; Color prints 3.5 x 4 - 5x7. (Box 59, Folder 916)
      Chef and shipboard buffet, 1964; Falconry, 1967. LSR sailing with friends, 1972. Unidentified friends in Caribbean. Native dancers, glass-bottomed boat over coral reef, and other unidentified views, undated. Aerial view of East River shoreline, 1978. Unidentified views. LSR and MFR at unidentified event; photos dated 1975 November were originally filed in envelope (erroneously) labeled "30th Wedding Anniversary." Undated and unidentified color negatives (Caribbean, sailboat, guests).
    - YWCA World Tour, 1963; Album, 7.75 x 6.75 x 1.5, with Color 5x7 prints. (Box 59, Folder 917)
      LSR and MFR at Mauna Kea; Africa, India, Southeast Asia. Prints (enlargements) dated September 1963.
    - YWCA World Tour, 1962-1963; Color slides (80). (Box 60, Folder 918)
      YWCA Round the World short version. MFR in Hawaii, Japan, Hong Kong, Philippines, England, Belgium, Turkey, Greece, Lebanon, Jordan, Egypt, Uganda, Tanganyika, India, Burma, Thailand, Korea. National Geographic Society photos by Otis Imboden. Slides removed from Carousel tray.
    - YWCA World Tour, 1962; 59 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 60, Folder 919)
      Hawaii, Japan, Hong Kong, Philippines. National Geographic Society photos by Otis Imboden. Includes LSR and MFR; son in Japan.
    - YWCA World Tour, 1963; 46 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 60, Folder 920)
      Belgium, Turkey, Greece, Lebanon, Baalbek, Jerusalem, Jordan. National Geographic Society photos by Otis Imboden. Includes MFR and LSR.
    - YWCA World Tour, 1963; 46 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 60, Folder 921)
      Uganda, Tanganika, Kenya. National Geographic Society photos by Otis Imboden. Includes LSR and MFR.
    - YWCA World Tour, 1963; 55 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 60, Folder 922)
      India, Burma, Thailand, Cambodia. National Geographic Society photos by Otis Imboden. Includes LSR and MFR.
    - YWCA World Tour, 1963 October; 14 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 60, Folder 923)
      File labeled "Denmark (MFR)." Trip presumably part of YWCA tour, but slides carry no marking other than date stamp.
    - YWCA World Tour (MFR), 1962-1963; 9 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 60, Folder 924)
      MFR meeting with women at various stops on her tour. File labeled "YWCA Extras." National Geographic Society photos by Otis Imboden.
    - YWCA World Tour, 1962-1963; 44 Color slides. (Box 60, Folder 925)
      Various unidentified National Geographic Society images from MFR's world tour. Includes images of MFR and of LSR. Slides marked "duplicate" and "Not for Publication."
  - Africa, 1940s; 2
    - Africa, 1940s; 7 black and white 3.5 x 4.75 photos (Box 61, Folder 926)
      MFR and LSR at airport; man handling lizard and birds
  - Asia, 1962 - 1990s; 3
    - Japan, 1962 November; 5x7 and 3.5x5 color prints; some glued to matboard frames. Some duplicate enlargements. (Box 61, Folder 927)
      LSR, MFR, and scenery. LSR showing photo of Buddha to deer.
    - Japan, Hong Kong, 1963, undated; 19 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. Slide jackets only partially glued, and film is slipping out from within them. Requires care in handling. (Box 61, Folder 928)
      File labeled "Japan, Hong Kong (MFR)." Airport and street views. May include Korean views
    - New Zealand, Hawaii, or Pacific Islands, 1974; 4x6 color prints (Box 61, Folder 929)
      LSR and MFR in Asia (New Zealand, Signs in English); Hawaii? MFR wearing lei and speaking. Prints are dated May 1995, but appear to be earlier. Dating based on date of Pacific Islands trip, 1974.
    - China (1), 1985 November; Color contact sheets and negatives. (Box 61, Folder 930)
      File labeled China Trip 1. Contact sheets (CS-59 - CS-60) and negatives.
    - China (2), 1985 November; Color contact sheets and negatives. (Box 61, Folder 931)
      File labeled China Trip 2. Contact sheets (CS-61 - CS-62) and negatives.
    - China (3), 1985 November; Color contact sheets and negatives. (Box 61, Folder 932)
      File labeled China Trip 3. Contact sheets (CS-63 - CS-64) and negatives.
    - China (4), 1985 November; Color contact sheets and negatives. (Box 61, Folder 933)
      File labeled China Trip 4. Contact sheets (CS-65 - CS-66) and negatives.
    - China (5), 1985 November; Color contact sheets and negatives. (Box 61, Folder 934)
      File labeled China Trip 5. Contact sheets (CS-67 - CS-68) and negatives.
    - China (6), 1985 November; Color contact sheets and negatives. (Box 61, Folder 935)
      File labeled China Trip 6. Contact sheets (CS-69 - CS-70) and negatives.
    - China (7), 1985 November; Color contact sheets and negatives. (Box 61, Folder 936)
      File labeled China Trip 7. Contact sheets (CS-71) and negatives.
    - China (8), 1985 November; Color contact sheets and negatives. (Box 61, Folder 937)
      File labeled China Trip 8. Contact sheets (CS-72 - CS-73) and negatives.
    - China, 1985 October-November; 3.5x5 color photos (Box 61, Folder 938)
      Inscription on envelope: "River boat trip (Guilin). Last day." LSR and MFR.
    - China, 1985 October-November; 3.5x5 color photos, with negatives (Box 61, Folder 939)
      Inscription on envelope: "Shanghai river boat trip." LSR and others; no MFR.
    - China; Hawaii; Wyoming: JY Ranch, 1985 October-November; 3.5x5 color photos, with negatives (Box 61, Folder 940)
      LSR and group; no MFR. Also Hawaii (flowers and beach); Wyoming: JY Ranch, with DR, Peggy R., and LSR family.
    - Malaysia and Indonesia?, 1990s; 4x6 color prints (Box 61, Folder 941)
      Includes photos of Penang City Hall; unidentified temples and buildings; LSR and MFR at unidentified ocean resort.
    - Thailand and Indonesia, 1990s; 4x6 color prints (Box 61, Folder 942)
      LSR, MFR, with Leonard and Caroline Firestone; artwork.
  - Canada, 1967; 4
    - Expo 67 (Montreal, Quebec), 1967; Color 3x5-5x7 prints. (Box 61, Folder 943)
      LSR, MFR, touring fair with 3 unidentified couples. Some prints dated August 1967.
  - Caribbean, 1950s - 1989; 5
    - General, mid-1950s; 77 color slides. (Box 61, Folder 944)
      Images from various rolls including MFR and LSR family at Caneel, NAR and Tod, Babs and Jean Mauze, and others. Caneel Bay, Sandy Cay, IBEC housing construction, one image of the Dauntless.
    - General (1 of 5), 1954; 36 color slides. (Box 61, Folder 945)
      Venezuela, including Avila Hotel, Caracas, University, views from IBEC offices, Valencia, Firestone plant, Inlaca milk plant, cattle. Includes MFR, Bill C. Includes descriptive list.
    - General (2 of 5), 1954; 36 color slides. (Box 62, Folder 946)
      Trinidad and Tobago, including Simla, William Beebe's tropical research station; Port of Spain, Fort Hill, Pigeon Beach. Dauntlessin harbor at St. George, Grenada. Includes images of Beebe, MFR, Roger Firestone. Includes descriptive list.
    - General (3 of 5), 1954; 36 color slides. (Box 62, Folder 947)
      Grenada, St. Lucia, Pigeon Island, Martinique, St. Pierre, Dominica. Includes MFR, "Beezie," Roger Cottrel, Ken B, John Archibald. Includes descriptive list.
    - General (4 of 5), 1954; 36 color slides. (Box 62, Folder 948)
      Archibald house, Guadeloupe, English Harbor, Antigua, Mill Reef Club, Saba Harbor. Includes images of MFR, and of the Dauntless in harbor and at sea. Includes descriptive list.
    - General (5 of 5), 1954; 35 color slides. (Box 62, Folder 949)
      Caneel Bay, Dauntless, Sugar Mill,
    - General, 1954 October-November; 34 color slides; color 3.5x5 Kodachrome prints. (Box 62, Folder 950)
      Includes Caneel Bay, San Juan, Dorado. Includes some images with MFR, LSR, and others.
    - Barbados, circa 1954; Color 3.5x5 Pavelle prints. Slight curling. (Box 62, Folder 951)
      Views. Includes MFR, man spearfishing.
    - Barbados, Haiti, Dominican Republic, Martinique, circa 1954; 17 color slides. (Box 62, Folder 952)
      Includes some images of MFR.
    - Caneel Bay and Virgin Islands, mid-1950s; CARD FILE BOX 3.5x5 color Pavelle prints. Badly curled. (Box O 121)
      LSR, MFR, NAR; Allston Boyer, (Ward Canaday), and others; buildings, scenery, Caneel Bay construction. MFR drawing. Photo envelope printed December 1953.
    - Caneel Bay and Cruz Bay, circa 1954; Color 3.5x5 Pavelle prints. Slight curling. (Box 62, Folder 953)
      Views. Includes some construction images, MFR painting, NAR.
    - Dorado Beach, PR, mid-1950s; Color 3.5x5 Pavelle prints. Slight curling. (Box 62, Folder 954)
      Views of Dorado, with some duplicates. Includes unidentified group photo of 14 men on beach, and 1 image of IBEC houses.
    - St. Thomas and St. Croix, circa 1954; Color 3.5x5 Pavelle prints. Slight curling. (Box 62, Folder 955)
      Some images are also found on slides filed under Trips: Caribbean, 1954 October-November.
    - San Juan, 1954 November; Color 3.5x5 Pavelle prints. Slight curling. (Box 62, Folder 956)
      Views of fort and water. Includes LSR, Allston Boyer, and others.
    - Bermuda? and Caneel Bay, 1956 November; 3.5x3.5 color prints in small 4 x 4.25 album, with negatives. Color faded. (Box 62, Folder 957)
      LSR, MFR, Abby R. Mauze; NAR at Caneel? Prints dated week of November 17, 1956. For better-quality copy of print of LSR and MFR see Trips: Vessels: General, 1950s-1991 (under 1956)
    - Caneel Bay, 1959 December; Color 5x7 enlargements. (Box 62, Folder 958)
      Views of Caneel Bay resort, taken from onboard the Wayfarer. MFR on board ship and in hammock at Caneel.
    - Caneel Bay, 1963-1964; 43 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 63, Folder 959)
      LSR on terrace of Cottage 7, sailing, views.
    - Dorado Beach, 1963, 1965; 15 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 63, Folder 960)
      File labeled "Dorado (MFR)." Beach, coast, palms in storm. Includes image of LSR?
    - Little Dix Bay, 1964-1966; 49 color slides, removed from wooden slide cabinet. (Box 63, Folder 961)
      LSR and friends at Little Dix. Images mainly of fishing and boating. Includes some images from Queen's visit.
    - Caneel Bay, 1969 March; Color 3.5 x 3.5 prints; negatives. (Box 63, Folder 962)
      LSR with unidentified friends. Includes photos of LSR on beach; birds, flowers.
    - Sea Star, 1971 February; Color 3.5 x 3.5 prints and 5x7 enlargements;some color negatives. (Box 63, Folder 963)
      LSR with Ethan and Elizabeth Hitchcock and others, on board Sea Star. Negatives from same envelope are of grandchildren at 834 Fifth Ave apartment.
    - Sea Star, 1972 March; Two sets of 3.5 x 3.5 color snapshots; some negatives. (Box 63, Folder 964)
      MFR sitting on bench with Sea Star in bay in background; Sea Star anchored in bay; LSR and MFR with Guy and Georgette Rutherfurd, Marian Heiskell, and others. Views from ship and of the ship; LSR standing by cannon.
    - Sea Star, 1972 March; 5x7 color print in 11.5 x 9.5 mat. Photo faded and surface crackled. (Box 63, Folder 965)
      Enlarged image of MFR sitting on bench with Sea Star in bay in background. Photo removed from frame
    - Sea Star, 1972 March-April; Color prints: 3.5 x 3.5 snapshots, 5x7 enlargements. Enlargements of images from folder 964. (Negatives and slides in separate folder, below.) (Box 63, Folder 966)
      LSR, MFR, and friends, in Caribbean. Includes Guy and Georgette Rutherfurd, Marian Heiskell, Elizabeth and Ethan Hitchcock, (John and Eleanor French).
    - Sea Star (Negatives and Slides), 1972 March-April; Color negatives and 7 color slides (see prints in preceding folder). (Box 63, Folder 967)
      LSR, MFR, and friends, in Caribbean. Includes (Marian Heiskell), Elizabeth and Ethan Hitchcock, (John and Eleanor French), Georgette and Guy Rutherfurd. Nice photos of LSR and MFR. Includes negative of MFR portrait seated overlooking Sea Star in bay.
    - Nassau, The Bahamas, circa 1973 January; Color snapshots 3x4, and negatives. (Box 63, Folder 968)
      LSR, Georgette Rutherfurd, and other unidentified people. Golfing.
    - Caneel Bay, 1975 December; Color 3.5 x 5 prints; negatives. (Box 63, Folder 969)
      LSR and MFR on board ship; views of Caneel Bay.
    - Caneel Bay, 1988 December 28 - 1989 January 1; Album, 8.5 x 14 x 1, with 4x6 color prints (Box 64, Folder 970)
      Visit to Caneel Bay with day trip to Sandy Cay. MFR, LSR, and family.
    - Caneel Bay, 1988 December 28 - 1989 January 1; Negatives (Box 64, Folder 971)
      Negatives presumably for some of the photos in the album of the same date. (Negatives originally filed under "Vessels.")
  - Europe, 1930s - 2000; 6
    - Greece, Undated (1930s-1940s?); Black and white prints, approx. 3.5x5, slightly curled (Box 64, Folder 972)
      MFR, LSR at Acropolis; several photos taken from plane of coastline and topography
    - Ireland, 1967 September 24-October 1; Color 3.5x3.5 prints, in 10x10x1.75 flip album. Some photos detached from pages. (Box 64, Folder 973)
      LSR and MFR and unidentified man.
    - Norway, 1974 August; 5x7 color prints (Box 64, Folder 974)
      LSR, MFR trip on Sea Star with Floyd and Kime Hall. Photo box with notation: "LSR MFR prints eliminated." Prints dated August 1974.
    - Norway, 1974 August; 5x7 color prints (Box 64, Folder 975)
      Photo box with notation: "LSR MFR prints eliminated." Prints dated August 1974.
    - Norway, 1974 August; 5x7 color prints (Box 64, Folder 976)
      Photo box with notation: "LSR MFR prints eliminated." Prints dated August-November 1974. On Sea Star. Photos include LSR, MFR.
    - Norway, 1974; 5x7 color prints (Box 65, Folder 977)
      Photo box with notation: "LSR MFR prints eliminated." Prints dated July-November 1974. On Sea Star. Photos include LSR, MFR, Leonard Firestone, Ethan and Elizabeth Hitchcock, and others.
    - France, 1975 May; OVERSIZED 11x14 color print; some cracking, curling, and fading. (Box O 122)
      Photo of a rainbow over a village and fields. Taken by MFR on the Princess cruise on the Marne Canal, around May 8, 1975. Note enclosed from Justin Dart describing photo.
    - Aegean Cruise, 1979; Color contact sheet and negatives. (Box 65, Folder 978)
      Three images on contact sheet (CS-56) and negatives. Includes images of Lynda Byrd Johnson (Robb).
    - Greece, Rome, England, 1979 Summer; Color negatives, slides, and snapshots, housed in 3.75 x 5.25 envelopes. (Box O 144)
      Negatives file (plus slides and a few prints) of LSR and MFR visit to Greece wiith Lady Bird Johnson and others. Negatives housed in captioned envelopes, numbered 1-79. Includes some images from Rome (Princess Boncompagni); England with Dolans and Mazes; and son at Pocantico. File also includes some envelopes of slides from Woodstock and JY Ranch (described elsewhere), and negatives of Mrs. Bobst and dog, spring 1981.
    - France (Giverny), 1982; Two 4x6 color photos. (Box 65, Folder 979)
      Two photos of LSR and MFR in garden, one with John and Eleanor French.
    - Switzerland? (Maze visit), circa 1985; Color negative strips. (Box 65, Folder 980)
      Color negatives of prints in personal photos envelope 500, 042.1. File labeled "Maze trip in Switzerland" (LSR and MFR appear to have visited Margaret Maze and Etienne Maze in France in 1987.)
    - France and Germany, 1987 May; Color 3x5 prints loosely inserted in 6.5 x 6.25 diary album. (Box 65, Folder 981)
      MFR trip diary, for May 5-19. LSR, MFR, visit to Mr. and Mrs. Etienne Maze at Burie; Colmar, Baden-Baden. Photos inserted in album (but not attached), along with postcards and souvenirs. Nice photo of LSR and MFR. File includes trip itinerary.
    - England and France, 1980s; OVERSIZED Album Color 4x6 prints in 12.5 x 14 magnetic album. (Box O 122)
      LSR and MFR in England and France (includes Rodin Museum, Giverney with Gerald Van der Kemp). Album also includes some unidentified construction photos and views of New York.
    - France (Giverny) and England, 1988; Color 4x6 prints in small softcover album; negatives. (Box 65, Folder 982)
      LSR, MFR, Florence and Gerald Van der Kemp; Connaught Hotel, Sow and Pigs pub. Photos dated May 1988.
    - Italy (Venice), 1988; 4x6 color prints in paper album covers (originally elastic bound). Some photos are sticking on edges. (Box 65, Folder 983)
      Photos dated June 1988. LSR, MFR, Leonard and Caroline Firestone, and others. Two sets of photos, one of which is double exposed.
    - Russia, 1989; 4x6 color prints (Box 65, Folder 984)
      LSR, MFR, and other unidentified couples. Photos dated October 1989.
    - France, 1994 October; Color 5x7 prints. (Box 65, Folder 985)
      LSR and MFR at Chateau de St. Maigrin and golfing; with Margaret Maze, Yolande de Cazanove, Juliette Ford, and Jean and Thierry Feray. (Photos sent from Burie by Margaret Maze?)
    - France (Le Voyage des Bons Vivants), 2000 April 11-24; 4x6 color prints glued to 6.5x9.75 pages. Note: Yellow post-it notes used as labels. (Box 65, Folder 986)
      Unbound album in 10 sections, documenting trip, including barge trip on Le Bon Vivant from Chatillon-sur-Loire to Nemours. Travel with Guy and Georgie Rutherfurd, and Evan and Marie Galbraith. Section 1: Paris.
    - France (Le Voyage des Bons Vivants), 2000 April 11-24; 4x6 color prints glued to 6.5x9.75 pages. Note: Yellow post-it notes used as labels. (Box 65, Folder 987)
      Unbound album in 10 sections, documenting trip, including barge trip on Le Bon Vivant from Chatillon-sur-Loire to Nemours. Travel with Guy and Georgie Rutherfurd, and Evan and Marie Galbraith. Sections 2-3: Chatillon - Rogny, April 16-17.
    - France (Le Voyage des Bons Vivants), 2000 April 11-24; 4x6 color prints glued to 6.5x9.75 pages. Note: Yellow post-it notes used as labels. (Box 65, Folder 988)
      Unbound album in 10 sections, documenting trip, including barge trip on Le Bon Vivant from Chatillon-sur-Loire to Nemours. Travel with Guy and Georgie Rutherfurd, and Evan and Marie Galbraith. Sections 4-5: Rogny - Montargis, April 18-19.
    - France (Le Voyage des Bons Vivants), 2000 April 11-24; 4x6 color prints glued to 6.5x9.75 pages. Note: Yellow post-it notes used as labels. (Box 65, Folder 989)
      Unbound album in 10 sections, documenting trip, including barge trip on Le Bon Vivant from Chatillon-sur-Loire to Nemours. Travel with Guy and Georgie Rutherfurd, and Evan and Marie Galbraith. Sections 6-7: Montargis - Nemours, April 19-20.
    - France (Le Voyage des Bons Vivants), 2000 April 11-24; 4x6 color prints glued to 6.5x9.75 pages. Note: Yellow post-it notes used as labels. (Box 66, Folder 990)
      Unbound album in 10 sections, documenting trip, including barge trip on Le Bon Vivant from Chatillon-sur-Loire to Nemours. Travel with Guy and Georgie Rutherfurd, and Evan and Marie Galbraith. Section 8: Nemours, April 21.
    - France (Le Voyage des Bons Vivants), 2000 April 11-24; 4x6 color prints glued to 6.5x9.75 pages. Note: Yellow post-it notes used as labels. (Box 66, Folder 991)
      Unbound album in 10 sections, documenting trip, including barge trip on Le Bon Vivant from Chatillon-sur-Loire to Nemours. Travel with Guy and Georgie Rutherfurd, and Evan and Marie Galbraith. Sections 9-10: Chateau St. Aubin (Gay and Edmond Lahaye-Jousselin), Chantilly, Paris, April 22-24.
    - France, 2000 April 11-24; Small album 6.5 x 4.75, with 4x6 color prints (Box 66, Folder 992)
      Barge trip on Le Bon Vivant. LSR, Evan and Marie Galbraith, Florence Van der Kemp, Guy and Georgie Rutherfurd. Album created by Georgie Rutherfurd; undated note enclosed.
  - Mexico, 1982 - 2002; 7
    - San Miguel de Allende, 1982-1993, undated; Mainly 4x6 color prints; some 3.5x5 prints (Box 66, Folder 993)
      General file with dated and undated photos. LSR, MFR, Van der Kemps, Rutherfords, Galbraiths. Nice photo of LSR and MFR.
    - San Miguel de Allende, 1983 March; 3x5 color prints; loose album pages (somewhat dirty but intact) (Box 66, Folder 994)
      LSR, MFR, Guy and Georgie Rutherfurd; (Gerald and Florence Van der Kemp).